Guide to the Pat Williams Papers 1979-1997
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Wilderness, 1979-1980; Series VIII; 6.0 linear feet
  - Northern Rockies Ecosystems Protection Act, 1992-1994 and undated (Box-folder 153/2)
  - Wilderness Dams, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 153/3)
  - Constituent Letters against the Montana Wilderness Association, 1991 (Box-folder 153/4)
  - Constituent Letters against the Montana Wilderness Association, 1991 (Box-folder 153/5)
  - Grizzly Bear Recover Plan, Cabinet and Yaak Regions, 1992 (Box-folder 153/6)
  - Beartooth, 1991 and undated (Box-folder 153/7)
  - Badger-Two Medicine, 1990-1992 and undated (Box-folder 153/8)
  - Sweet Grass Mining, 1993-1995 and undated (Box-folder 153/9)
  - H.R.2032, S. 550, Nez Perce National Historic Park, 1991 (Box-folder 153/10)
  - H.R. 5898, Rattlesnake Wilderness, Correspondence, 1978-1980 and undated (Box-folder 154/1)
  - H.R. 5898, S. 3072, Rattlesnake Wilderness, Bills and Amendments, 1979-1980 and undated (Box-folder 154/2)
  - H.R. 5898, Rattlesnake Wilderness, Clippings and Correspondence, 1979-1980 and undated (Box-folder 154/3)
  - H.R. 5898, Rattlesnake Wilderness, Reports, Maps, Data, 1978-1986 and undated (Box-folder 154/4)
  - H.R. 5898, Rattlesnake Wilderness, Testimonies, Maps, Data, 1978-1980 and undated (Box-folder 154/5)
  - H.R. 5898, Testimonies and Statements, 1979 (Box-folder 155/1)
  - H.R. 5898, Testimonies and Statments, 1979 and undated (Box-folder 155/2)
  - Rattlesnake, Limits of Acceptable Change based on Management Direction, 1992 (Box-folder 155/3)
  - General Land Resource Management, 1987-1996 (Box-folder 155/4)
  - Beaverhead Timber Management Plan, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 155/5)
- Audio and Video, 1979-1996; Series IX; 10.5 linear feet; 124 items
  This series contains Williams' public collection of video tape materials collected while in Congress. VHS, Beta, two-inch, and 3/4 inch formats are inter-filed. This series contains recordings of selected floor speeches, floor debates, public service announcements, messages to constituents transmitted to Montana broadcast stations, nationally broadcast news segments, panel discussions, speeches to professional organizations, and materials produced by Montana organizations and individuals related to Pat Williams' congressional activities. This collection also contains two phone conversations with radio stations recorded on audiocassette tapes.
  - P. Williams announces legislation to establish Rattlesnake Wilderness with a proposed education center under USFS/UM joint operation (6 segments), 12-3-1979; 239(IX)1; 9 min., VHS tape, good quality (copy of orig. on 2" vt. reel)
  - P. Williams announces legislation to aid independent oil drillers to open new wells on public lands, 12-18-1979; 239(IX)2; 1:30 min., VHS tape, good quality, (copy of orig. on 2" vt. reel)
  - The Lawmakers - Profiles the debate between Congress and Reagan Administration re: funding for national ed. programs, 6-23-1983; 239(IX)3; 60 min., VHS tape, No sound during 1st Williams statement
  - Germ Warfare Segment, NBC Overnight, Williams author of legislation to investigate use of U.S. Army POWs in Japan as specimens for germ experiments (2nd of two segments), 9-29-1983; 239(IX)4; 10 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Pat Williams for Congress, 1984, Maney Productions, Butte, series of paid political announcements (P. Williams 34 of 5 segments), 239(IX)5; 5 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Pat Williams and commit. hearing re: Elderly, Maney Productions, (unprocessed as of 8-22-97), 1984; 239(IX)6; 1" reel
  - "Pat Williams Office Use": News segments. re: Montana Wilderness/Roadless area legislation (P. Williams, M. Baucus, J. Melcher), 1984; 239(IX)7; 30 min., VHS tape, poor video
  - Debates re: Grace Commission, Williams and P. Grace, 10-4-1984; 239(IX)8; Beta tape, good quality
    1) Today Show, 10 min.
    2) MacNeil/Lehrer Hr., 10 min.
    3) Crossfire (blank during com. break), 20 min.
    4) Williams reaction to Reagan flat tax plan, 20 min.
  - P. Williams Floor Speeches, etc, 1985; 239(IX)9; Beta tape, good quality
    1-16 40th Anniversary First Nuclear Test - floor speech joined in progress, 10 min.
    7-16 Special Order VISTA - floor speech joined in progress, 10 min.
    7-26 Asbestos Bill Introduction - floor speech (full text), 20 min.
    9-9 Polygraph - Nightwatch segment - good audio debate with Larry Sherwood, 10 min, poor video
    10-10 Endow. for Arts and Human. - FS (full text) and floor debate, 20 min.
  - Series of news segments on corporate employee screening techniques, partic. handwriting analysis and polygraphs, 6-7-1985; 239(IX)10; Beta tape, fair quality
    Includes statements from Williams, 30 min., Floor debate of NEAH granting procedure bill, joined in progress, 30 min.
  - Fighting Chance - Olympic boxing, 30 min., Beta tape, good audio;(promo) - statements from Williams, poor video, 6-21-1985; 239(IX)11
  - Women's Campaign Fund, 8-30-1985; 239(IX)12; 1" reel
  - Montana Democrats: "Keeping Our Word", 11-4-1985; 239(IX)13; 1" reel
  - Suspension: Handicapped Children's Protection Act - floor debate with Williams - joined in progress, 20 min., Beta tape, fair quality 11-14-85, Congressional Award - floor debate of Love Canal special award for EPA clean-up (Williams not present), 11-12-1985; 239(IX)14
  - Don Peoples Tribute - Mayor/Chief Exec. of Butte/Silver Bow - including Williams statement, 1986; 239(IX)15; 30 min., VHS tape, poor video
  - Williams-Allen Debates, 1986; 239(IX)16; 30 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - Face the State - Int. with Williams re: Reagan Administration's 1986 budget prop., Spt. 86; 239(IX)17; 30 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - "MTN News" - It's Your Business - debate: min. wage, Williams on panel, VHS tape, good quality, 30 min. 3-28-86, "Earth First" - Multiple MTN news, 5 min., 3-10-1986; 239(IX)18
  - Williams Floor speech - aid to immigrants and disadvantaged children (jip), Beta tape, good quality, 4 min. Today Show - disc. with Williams on ethics of Earth First!, fair video -10 min., poor audio, 3-28-1986; 239(IX)19
  - Jonathan Kozol and Williams discussion Good Morning America: Adult Illiteracy, 9-3-1986; 239(IX)20; 10 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - CNN Profiles in Congress: Williams, 1987; 239(IX)21; 10 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - Education Budget - Williams, 4-8-1987; 239(IX)22
    Floor speech re: Reagan Administration budget, (jip), VHS tape, good quality, 15 min. 5-13-87, DOD Midgetman - Williams floor speech, and R. Marlenee response, 30 min. 10-13-87, Montana Wilderness Bill - Floor debate, Williams R. Marlenee as principal speakers, 30 min. 11-4-87, Polygraph Bill - Williams floor speech, 10 min.
  - "Rep. Williams #5, show #2" Williams announces for creation of the National Center for Vocational Rehabilitation, Research, and Training for Rural America at University of Montana (2 segs.), 9-8-1987; 239(IX)23
    8 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams #6, show #2," duplicate of above (#23), 8 min., 9-8-1987; 239(IX)24; 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Williams Governor Speech, - speech in Missoula declining Gov. race, 9-19-1987; 239(IX)25
    30 min., Beta tape, poor video -poor audio
  - Polygraph Bill (con't from #22)- Williams floor speech joined in progress, 11-4-1987; 239(IX)26; 15 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - Williams speech to National. Community Action Foundation, 12-23-1987; 239(IX)27; 30 min., Beta tape, fair quality
  - "Rep. Williams #1, show #5", 1-12-1988; 239(IX)28; 3/4" tape, good quality
    1) Midgetman Missile - Williams response to funding bill, 2 min.
    2) Wall St. Reforms - Williams response, 2 min.
    3) U.S.-Canada Trade Pact - Williams response, 2 min.
  - A Chance for Our Children - Sen. John Melcher, 1-16-1988; 239(IX)29; 30 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - A Place to Soar Flathead Economic Development - gift to P. Williams, 1-27-1988; 239(IX)30; 30 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - Great Northwest Log Haul (lumber protest) KECI-TV, 5-13-1988; 239(IX)31; 30 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - DNC Econ. Forum: "Building the Am. Dream" - Williams, panel member, 6-2-1988; 239(IX)32; 60 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - Rep. P. Williams #2 -, 6-16-1988; 239(IX)33; 6 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - MacNeil/Lehrer News Hr., "Timber Tempest" - re: Montana wilderness bill, 8-8-1988; 239(IX)34; 10 min., VHS tape, fair quality
  - More than a Map: The people speak from the heart on Wilderness in Montana, six people in diff. wilderness settings talk about the meaning of wilderness (No bios, intros, or description of place), 9-10-1988; 239(IX)35; 1 hr., Beta tape, fair video, inconsistent audio
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #1, show #2", 10-6-1988; 239(IX)36; 6 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #4, show #1-, 10-6-1988; 239(IX)37; 6 min. "3/4" tape, good quality, cuts in mid. of 1st statement
    Williams response to Bus Admin. threats to veto wilderness management bill, 6 min.
  - Floor Speeches, etc., 10-20-1988; 239(IX)38
  - Stoltz Lumber - video of slide show Present. lobbying against Beaverhead National. Forest Plan of 1989, 239(IX)39; 20 min., VHS tape, fair quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #4, show #2 -, 3-8-1989; 239(IX)40; 6 min., 3/4" tape, good sound, poor video
  - Yellowstone Park Fires, ABC News - taped for P. Williams, 6-12-1989; 239(IX)41; 30 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - Montana In Congress: The Centennial Delegation - profile of Williams and other Montana members of the 1989-90 Congress, 7-1989; 239(IX)42; 15 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #3"- Williams resp. to timber harvest agreement cuts in mid statement, 12-13-1989; 239(IX)43; 10 min., 3/4" tape, fair quality
  - Rep. Williams, 1-23-1990; 239(IX)44; tape #3", 3/4" tape, good quality
    1) Williams resp. to Cong. Over-ride of Pres. Bush veto of "Chinese Students Bill," 2 min.
    2) Williams ann. re: Badger-Two Medicine legislation (Blackfoot Reservation), 3 min.
    3) Williams ann. re: payroll tax decrease legislature, 3 min.
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #5"- Williams reaction to Sen. Burns bill re: wilderness management, 1-25-1990; 239(IX)45; 6 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Williams re-election filing announcement, 3-13-1990; 239(IX)46; 2 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Williams re-election filing announcement (duplicate of above, #46), 3-13-1990; 239(IX)47; 2 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #3, show #1", 4-25-1990; 239(IX)48; 6 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #6, show #1" (duplicate of above, #50), 4-25-1990; 239(IX)49; 6 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #3"- Williams ann. what to expect from Cong. summer session - lumber export bill, 6-4-1990; 239(IX)50; 3 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #8"(duplicate of above, #50), 6-4-1990; 239(IX)51; 3 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #2, show #1"- Williams reaction to budget negotiations and Bush Administration tax proposals, 7-9-1990; 239(IX)52; 5 min., 3/4" tape, fair quality/ deteriorating
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #1, show #1"- Williams reaction to Sen. Burns opposition to Lolo-Kootenai accords, 7-23-1990; 239(IX)53; 6 min., 3/4" tape, fair quality -some rolls in picture
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #3, show #1"(duplicate of above, #53), 7-23-1990; 239(IX)54; 6 min., 3/4" tape fair quality - same problems.
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #1, show #1"- Williams responds to prog. of budget summit proposed budget balancing plan, 7-30-1990; 239(IX)55; 4 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #4, show #1"- Williams reaction to budget burden of U.S. military presence in the Middle East - cuts in mid of 1st statement., 8-13-1990; 239(IX)56; 4 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Bitterroot Views - interview with P. Williams re: Guinn Tower Project, war in Iraq, loss of Montana Congressional seat, Montana wilderness bill, SLs, NEA, and Bitterroot development, 8-22-1990; 239(IX)57; 25 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #4"- Williams resp. to continued U.S. military presence in the Middle East, 9-5-1990; 239(IX)58; 4 min., 3/4" tape, good quality- cuts in middle of statement
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #7" (Same as above, #60 - KCFW countdown edited over the begining of statement), 9-5-1990; 239(IX)59; 4 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Williams-Johnson Debate, 10-30-1990; 239(IX)60; 1 hr., VHS tape, good quality
  - P. Williams, Key. Speaker TRI-FUND Conference (Labor Management), 2-8-1991; 239(IX)61; 30 min., VHS tape, good quality
  - P. Williams, Address to Democratic Officer Convention, Buttem, 6-29-1991; 239(IX)62; 30 min, VHS tape, poor video audio
  - Williams: PSA Nat'l Home Care Week, 11-26-1991; 239(IX)63; 4 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Response to campaign spending" - Williams statement re: offer to limit campaign spending for the 1992 race against R Marlenee, 239(IX)64; 3 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #1, show #2"- Williams ann. of Canadian wheat import letter sent to Sec. of Com. Mike Espy, 9-23-1993; 239(IX)65; 6 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - "Rep. Williams, tape #2, show #2" (duplicate of above, #65), 9-23-1993; 239(IX)66; 6 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Williams, Remarks on 1994 Congress. Campaign (Harriman Com. Center), 239(IX)67
    2 min., 3/4" tape, good quality
  - Changing State of the Arts, Oct. 14, 1995; 239(IX)68
  - Ron Melcher and Pat Williams Debate, Kalispell, Montana, Aug. 18, undated; 239(IX)69
  - Pat Williams Campaign Commercial, "Courage", 239(IX)70
  - Campaign Commercials, "Issues," "Stampede," and "Logs", 1990; 239(IX)71
  - Pat Williams Campaign Commercial, "Spot from Hell", 239(IX)72
  - Pat Williams Campaign Endorsments, 1990; 239(IX)73
  - Pat Williams Campaign Endorsments, 1990; 239(IX)74
  - Pat Williams Campaign Commercial, "Fling Ad", March 9, 1992; 239(IX)75
  - Bob Marshall Alliance Commercial, "Arnold Bolle-Wildlands/Williams", June 4, 1987; 239(IX)76
  - Pat Williams Campaign Commercials, Demo Tape, May 1, 1987; 239(IX)77
  - Pat Williams giving speech in Seattle, Spring 1995; 239(IX)78
  - Joint Meeting in Commemoration for the 200th Anniversary of Congress, March 2, 1989; 239(IX)79
  - Pat Williams giving speech at Truman Dinner, Billings, Montana, April 13, 1996; 239(IX)80
  - Pat Williams Budget Speech to Community Action Group, undated; 239(IX)81
  - Pat Williams remarks about NEA Flag Amendment, undated; 239(IX)82
  - Pat Williams on Health Care, October 30, 1991; 239(IX)83
  - Pat Williams Campaign Commercial, "Mister No", October 23, 1992; 239(IX)84
  - Pat Williams speaking on the House of Representatives Floor about National Endowment for the Arts, undated; 239(IX)85
  - Pat Williams speaking on the House of Representatives Floor about National Endowment for the Arts, June 20, 1996; 239(IX)86
  - Four Pat Williams commercials, Nov. 1980; 239(IX)87; 2 inch video
  - Two Pat Williams commercials, undated; 239(IX)88; 2 inch video
  - Four Pat Williams commercials, Sept. 1980; 239(IX)89; 2 inch video
  - Pat Williams commercials, May 1980; 239(IX)90; 2 inch video
  - Pat Williams commercial, Sept. 1982; 239(IX)91; 2 inch video
  - Green Mansion Promos, undated; 239(IX)92; 2 inch video
  - Pat Williams for congress commercial, undated; 239(IX)93; 2 inch video
  - Job Corps, May 20, 1985; 239(IX)94; beta video
  - Pat Williams on the house floor, May 20, 1985; 239(IX)95; beta video
  - Glacier Park, Sept. 3, 1985; 239(IX)96; beta video
  - Its Your Business, Minimum wage, Nov. 11, 1985; 239(IX)97; beta video
  - Pat Williams and Grace, one on one, Nov. 1985; 239(IX)98; beta video
  - Jeanette Rankin, undated; 239(IX)99; beta video
  - "Montana's Election Preview" Western Congressional Candidate, 1984; 239(IX)100; beta video
  - President Clinton, Dave Dickerson, Don Read, telephone conversation recorded by KUFM, Dec. 12, 1995; 239(IX)101
  - Conversations: Pat Williams, recorded by KEMC, undated; 239(IX)102
  - Conversations: Pat Williams, recorded by KEMC, duplicate of 239(IX)102, 239(IX)103
  - Montana's First Century with Pat Williams, May 11, 1992; 239(IX)104
  - Face the State, July 1994; 239(IX)105
  - Challenges To the Constitution with Pat Williams and John Milewski, undated; 239(IX)106
  - 700 Club, March 22, 1990; 239(IX)107
  - Pat Williams on C-Span discussing Newspaper articles about healthcare, January, 1996; 239(IX)108
  - Interview with Pat Williams, on KTVQ and KULR, undated; 239(IX)109
  - Healthcare Reform discussion on KPAX, June 22, 1994; 239(IX)110
  - Pat Williams and Ron Marlenee debate on PBS, 1992; 239(IX)111
  - Pat Williams with Rankin Family and Representative, undated; 239(IX)112
  - Pat Williams discussing the Persian Gulf Crisis, January 11, 1991; 239(IX)113
  - Pat Williams speaking at the United States High Altitude Speed Skating Foundation Banquet, Butte, Montana, November 15, 1985; 239(IX)114
  - The 700 Club containing clips of Pat Williams defending a position on the House floor, June 22, 1990; 239(IX)115
  - CBS News interview, Pat Williams discussing meat importing inspection, undated; 239(IX)116
  - Face the State followed by a Washington Press Confrence, January 1984; 239(IX)117
  - Crossfire and other television clips, December 10, 1984; 239(IX)118
  - Pat Williams television commericals, undated; 239(IX)119
  - Face the State, February, 1985; 239(IX)120
  - Face the State, May 31, 1985; 239(IX)121
  - Pat Williams discussing the arts, June, 1990; 239(IX)122
  - Pat Williams and Ron Marlenee debate, May 1, 1992; 239(IX)123
  - Pat Williams on C-Span, undated; 239(IX)124
- Guest Books and Student Portraits, 1979-1996; Series X; 1.0 linear foot
  This series consists of the guest books kept in Williams' D.C. office and of portraits produced by students of Williams. Most of the portraits are from Montana schools; the artists range in age from kindergarten to high school.
  The guest books are arranged chronologically; the three folders of student portraits are unarranged.
  - Guest Books, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 156/1)
  - Guest Books, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 156/2)
  - Guest Books, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 156/3)
  - Guest Books, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 156/4)
  - Guest Books, 1984-1996 (Box-folder 156/5)
  - Guest Books, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 156/6)
  - Guest Books, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 157/1)
  - Guest Books, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 157/2)
  - Guest Books, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 157/3)
  - Guest Books, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 157/4)
  - Christmas Cards, 1979-1996 (Box-folder 157/5)
  - Student Portraits of Pat, undated (Box-folder 157/6)
  - Student Portraits of Pat, undated (Box-folder 157/7)
  - Student Portraits of Pat, undated (Box-folder 157/8)
- Photographs, 1979-1996; Series XI; 1.0 linear foot
  This series contains portraits taken during Williams' time in Congress. Images are mostly of Williams and/or close associates at a variety of events. Photographs of events he attended, including Democratic National Conventions, are also included. Images are of both Montana and Washington, DC.
  - Pat Williams with two men at Veteran's Center in Billings, 1988; 239(XI):1 (Box 158/1)
  - Pat Williams with group of eleven at Veteran's Center, Billings, 1988; 239(XI):2 (Box 158/2)
  - Pat Williams next to unidentified man, Budget hearing, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):3 (Box 158/3)
  - Pat Williams with two unidentified men at Budget hearing, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):4 (Box 158/4)
  - Pat Williams at Budget hearing, undated; 239(XI):5 (Box 158/5)
  - Pat Williams speaking to Mrs. Boxer at Budget hearing, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):6 (Box 158/6)
  - Mrs. Boxer, Pat Williams, Mr. Miller, and unidentified man at Budget Hearing, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):7 (Box 158/7)
  - Mrs. Boxer, Pat Williams speaking into microphone, Budget hearing, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):8 (Box 158/8)
  - Pat Williams holding microphone, Budget hearing, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):9 (Box 158/9)
  - Budget Hearing Panel, Feb 1985; 239(XI):10 (Box 158/10)
  - Pat Williams speaking at School of Fine Arts Commencement, University of Montana--Missoula, 1990; 239(XI):11 (Box 158/11)
  - Pat Williams, C., with two unidentified men, Democratic National Convention, 1988; 239(XI):12 (Box 158/12)
  - Democratic National Convention, Atlanta, 1988; 239(XI):13 (Box 158/13)
  - Democratic National Convention, Atlanta, 1988; 239(XI):14 (Box 158/14)
  - Democratic National Convention, Atlanta, 1988; 239(XI):15 (Box 158/15)
  - Democratic National Convention, Atlanta, 1988; 239(XI):16 (Box 158/16)
  - Pat Williams with three unidentified people, PTA Convention, Helena, 1984; 239(XI):17 (Box 158/17)
  - Pat Williams addressing Montana legislature, 1991; 239(XI):18 (Box 158/18)
  - Pat Williams addressing Montana legislature, 1991; 239(XI):19 (Box 158/19)
  - Pat Williams addressing Montana legislature, 1991; 239(XI):20 (Box 158/20)
  - Lily Frandsen, Missoula Fair Parade, Aug. 1992; 239(XI):21 (Box 158/21)
  - Pat Williams with Pam Scheevz at Rocky Mountain Log Homes, 1991; 239(XI):22 (Box 158/22)
  - Jim Schueler and Pat Williams at Rocky Mountain Log Homes, 1991; 239(XI):23 (Box 158/23)
  - Pat Williams at the Cultural Congress, Billings, 1987; 239(XI):24 (Box 158/24)
  - Pat Williams in parade car, Butte, July 4, 1986; 239(XI):25 (Box 158/25)
  - Willie Andrews by Pat Williams Sign, Oct. 1986; 239(XI):26 (Box 158/26)
  - Pat Williams Speaking at Montana State Libraries Convention, Great Falls, 1990; 239(XI):27 (Box 158/27)
  - Montana State Libraries Convention, Great Falls, 1990; 239(XI):28 (Box 158/28)
  - Pat Williams unrolling paper at Montana State Library Convention, Great Falls, 1990; 239(XI):29 (Box 158/29)
  - Pat Williams holding Thankyou poster, Montana State Library Convention, Great Falls, 1990; 239(XI):30 (Box 158/30)
  - Mike Scotts daughter, 1992; 239(XI):31 (Box 158/31)
  - Kelsey and Caitlin Christopher at the fair, 1994; 239(XI):32 (Box 158/32)
  - Goo's House, 1992 campaign, 239(XI):33 (Box 158/33)
  - Pat Williams in parade, Crow Fair, 1991; 239(XI):34 (Box 158/34)
  - Ben Pease and Pat Williams prepare horse for parade, Crow Fair, 1991; 239(XI):35 (Box 158/35)
  - Roses Windy Boy and Bill Yellowtail fix horse banner, Crow Fair, 1991; 239(XI):36 (Box 158/36)
  - Pat Williams holding horse, Crow Fair, 1991; 239(XI):37 (Box 158/37)
  - Ben Pease MC's reception for Pat Williams in Angela Russell camp, Crow Fair, 1991; 239(XI):38 (Box 158/38)
  - Ben Pease and Pat Williams with two unidentified women, Crow Fair, 1991; 239(XI):39 (Box 158/39)
  - Pat Williams in Angela Russell Camp, Crow Fair, 1991; 239(XI):40 (Box 158/40)
  - Pat Williams in Parade at Crow Fair, 1991; 239(XI):41 (Box 158/41)
  - Kehle Louise Kankelborg in front of Pat Williams sign in Butte, undated; 239(XI):42 (Box 158/42)
  - Kehle Louise Kankelborg yelling by sign, Butte, undated; 239(XI):43 (Box 158/43)
  - Pat Williams and unidentified man with crowd at March to the Washington Monument, March 1987; 239(XI):44 (Box 158/44)
  - AFT members at AFL Convention, Great Falls, 1990; 239(XI):45 (Box 158/45)
  - Butte's Tony the Trader, Gov. Swinder, and Pat Williams, July 4, 1983; 239(XI):46 (Box 158/46)
  - Pat Williams at microphone, Retail Merchants, Florida, 1989; 239(XI):47 (Box 158/47)
  - Pat Williams at Microphone, 1989; 239(XI):48 (Box 158/48)
  - Pat Williams as referee in Boxing Match, undated; 239(XI):49 (Box 158/49)
  - Carpenter's Union, Bruce Morris, Paul Johnson, Pat Williams, Don Wilkins, John Kelly, 1988; 239(XI):50 (Box 158/50)
  - Elks recognition of Russell, George Klien, Pat Williams, Jack Cash, Frank Garland, Homer Huhn, Feb. 1985; 239(XI):51 (Box 158/51)
  - Museum Dedication, Flag given by Pat Williams, Alberton, Montana, July 15, 1989; 239(XI):52 (Box 158/52)
  - Chairman Mickey Pablo on dam safety tour, accompanied by others, undated; 239(XI):53 (Box 158/53)